钱德勒  莫妮卡
Ok, Chandler, Mon,
香蕉核桃松饼只剩一个了
there's only one bananna nut muffin left.
我先点的
Oh, I ordered mine first.
对  但我比你迅速
Yeah, but I'm, I'm so much faster...
给我
Give it to me.
不
No.
给我
Give it to me.
那给你吧
Ok, you can have it.
请慢慢享用你的咖啡
There you go, enjoy your coffee.
那一杯不是我的
That was there when I got here.
各位  你们绝对猜不到谁要来纽约
Hey you guys, you will never guess who's coming to New York.
菲比  在他吞下去以前说
Quick, Phoebe, tell us before he can swallow.
我在海军服役的男朋友莱恩
Oh ok, Ryan, that guy I went out with, who's in the Navy.
你有个当海军的男朋友吗
You went out with a guy in the Navy?
对  我在华盛顿广场公园
Yeah, I met him when I was playing guitar
演奏吉他的时候认识的
in Washington Square Park.
莱恩丢盐水太妃糖给我  因为他没有零钱
Ryan threw in salt water taffy 'cause he didn't have any change.
你就是因为这个写《盐水太妃糖男子》吗
Hey, is that when you wrote salt water taffy man?
不
No.
他是我的潜水艇男人
No, he is my submaring guy.
他两年出水一次
He resurfaces like every couple years
我们在一起过上最不可思议的三天
and we have the most amazing three days together.
只是他这一次要来两个礼拜
Only this time he's coming for two weeks.
整整两个礼拜  好耶
Two whole weeks, which means yay.
等等  你是说这个家伙每次一下水就是两年
So wait, this guy goes down for like two years at a time?
谁叫你舔我的松饼啊
That'll teach you to lick my muffin.
嗨
Hi.
怎么了
Oh no, what happened?
卡罗尔刚刚告诉我  小本出水痘了
Well, I just spoke to Carol. Ben's got the chicken pox.
不
Oh no.
所以如果你们还没出过
Yeah, so if you haven't already had it,
可能会被传染
chances are you're gonna get it.
我出过了
Well I've had it.
我也出过了
Yeah, I've had it.
出过
Had it.
我从来没出过  感觉我被遗弃了  看
Well, I've never had it, I feel so left out.  Oh look!
亲爱的  你又铺床了
Honey, you made the bed again.
我说过  你不用铺床的
I told you, you don't have to do that.
又不是夏令营
This isn't camp.
那我想昨晚的内裤大搜查
Ooh, then I guess the panty raid last night
完全没有道理了
was totally uncalled for.
我要去洗个澡
Ok, I am going to take a shower
今天我会唱杰姆·克劳奇的《李洛布朗》
and today I will be singing Jim Crochee's Leroy Brown.
莫妮卡  我有个问题
Monica...  Hey Mon, I have a question.
李洛他是全城最坏的小子
Is Leroy the baddest man in the whole damn town
还是全城最胖的小子
or the fattest man in the whole damn town?
最坏  不然那首歌
Baddest. Otherwise the song
就会叫《胖小子李洛布朗》了
would be Fat Fat Leroy Brown.
你在干什么
What're you doing?
只是在等你  甜心
Just waiting for you sweetie.
你在重新铺床吗
Are you remaking the bed?
对不起  你铺的样子完全没有问题
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You know what, the way you did it was just fine.
那你重新铺是因为...
Then, you're redoing it because...
说出来你会认为我疯了
If I tell you, you'll think I'm crazy.
你说不说都会有这个危险
You're pretty much running that risk either way.
你看
Ok, you see,
被子的商标不该在床的左上角
the duvet tag shouldn't be at the top left corner,
应该在床的右下角才对
it should be at the bottom right corner.
这不算很疯狂
Oh, well that's not so crazy.
我只是在帮你热身
I'm just easing you in.
好
Oh, alright.
你看到这些小花了吗
Alright, you see these little flower blossoms?
应该朝上不是朝下
They should be facing up, not down,
因为床头的位置  是太阳的方向
because, well, the head of the bed is where the sun would be.
你不再爱我了  是不是
You don't love me any more do you.
事实上  如果可能的话  我更爱你了
Actually, if it's possible, I love you more.
真的
Really?
那来吧
Wow, well then come on,
我教你怎么把卫生纸折出尖角来
I wanna show you how to fold the toilet paper into a point.
乔伊  如果你需要一个工作应急的话
Hey look Joey, I'm just saying if you need something to hold you over,
你可以在这里做初级的数据分析员
I can get you a job right here as an entry level processor.
这种工作难道不需要经验吗
But don't you need experience for a job like that?
要学也不难
It's not that hard to learn.
至于说别人看出你不知道自己在做什么
And as for people realizing you have no idea what you're doing,
你是个演员
hey, you're an actor.
那就扮演一个分析员
Act like a processor,
人们就会相信你是个分析员了
people will think you're a processor.
钱德勒  这是今早的预算表
Hey Chandler, here's this morning's projections.
谢了  斯科特·亚历山大
Hey thanks. Scott Alexander,
这位是乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbianni.
乔伊他也是一个数据分析员
Joey is a uh, fellow processor.
真的
No kidding.
是啊
Oh yeah yeah.
我分析  如果有人要分析  就会找我
I process. People want the processing, I'm the one they call.
你在哪儿高就
Where do you work?
我正在换工作
Uhh, well, right now I'm in between things.
你也知道的嘛  今天你还在分析
You know how it is. One day you're processing,
明天就没有那么多  可以分析的了
the next day you're not so much... processing any more.
我正在告诉乔伊  弗莱斯曼的部门缺人
I was just telling Joey about the opening in Fleischman's group.
弗莱斯曼的部门
Fleischman's group.
那你要记住  别碰他的三明治啊
Whatever you do, don't touch his sandwiches.
所有的分析员都是笨蛋吗
Are all you processors dorks?
你擦上这口红真美
Oh, this lipstick looks just great on you.
你美呆了  亲爱的  真的
You look fabulous honey, you really do.
你们确定吗  真的吗
Yeah? Are you sure, really.
瞧  美得不得了
You see, you look beautiful.
老天在上  灯调暗
For god sakes, dim the lights.
我好恐怖
I, I, I'm hideous.
不会有问题的
It's gonna be ok.
莱恩一直在水下
Ryan's been under water.
你屁股上没长海底寄生虫
He's just gonna be so glad that you
他就该谢天谢地了
don't have barnicles on your butt.
请进
Come in.
宝贝  我回来了
Hey baby, I'm back...
莱恩  你好吗
Hey Ryan, what's up?
你怎么了
What's goin' on?
不要  不要再往前走了  我出痘了
Well, no no, you have to stay back. I, I have the pox.
水痘还是天花痘
Chicken or small?
水痘(鸡)  真讽刺
Chicken. Which is so ironic
因为我根本就不吃肉
considering I'm a vegetarian.
那你为什么不在家里躺着休息
Why aren't you at home in bed?
因为我外婆没出过水痘
'Cause my, my grandmother's never had chicken pox.
拜托  告诉我你出过
Please, please tell me you have,
老天  我忘了你多可爱了
'cause oh my God, I forgot how cute you are.
抱歉  我没出过
I'm sorry, I never had 'em.
如果可以许一个愿
If I had one wish,
我要造个时光机器
it would be to build a time machine,
我要回到七岁  吉米·豪泽出水痘时
go back to when I was 7, when Jimmy Hauser had the chicken pox.
我会抓住那小子  整个人在我脸上蹭
I would grab that kid and rub him all over my face.
或许你也可以希望  我现在没出水痘
Yeah, or you know, you could just wish that I didn't have them now.
我可以看你的脸吗
Can I please see your face?
不行  你不会想看一张痘子脸的
Nope. You don't want to see a face covered with pox.
你脸上全是海湾我也不会在乎
Your face could be covered with lochs, I wouldn't care.
可是你讨厌鱼
And you hate fish. Oh.
你真贴心  好吧
That's so sweet, alright.
给你看吧
Ok, alright, you can see.
这就是我
This is me...
-很抱歉  -我很吓人
- Sorry. - Oh, I am scary.
抱歉  是闪电
Sorry, the lightning.
刚才的闪电是个不幸的巧合
Lightning was an unfortunate coincidence.
你很漂亮  很漂亮
You look lovely, lovely.
好讨厌
I hate this.
告诉你  我计划了最不可思议的两周
'Cause I tell you, I had the most amazing two weeks planned for us,
在我所有的计划里
and almost everything I had in mind,
我们都比现在亲密得多
we had to be a lot closer than this.
菲比
Phoebe,
我跟一群男人在钢管里关了八个月
I have spent the last eight months in a steel tube with men,
我心里盼着的就是这个时刻
thinking about this moment.
我不会让这些
I am not gonna let a bunch of
痒痒的小点挡在我们中间
itchy spots stand between us.
这是我得过的最浪漫的病
Ok, this is the most romantic disease I've ever had.
第一天上班怎么样
Hey, how's the first day goin'?
挺好的  就像你说的
Pretty good. It's like you said.
就是把数字从一栏  移到另一栏而已
It's mostly just putting numbers from one column into another column.
我跟你说过了
Well there you go.
而且同事们都很好
Hey and everbody is so nice.
我刚跟那个红发女士聊得很开心  叫金妮的
I just had a good talk with that lady with the red hair, Jeannie.
金妮  东岸的业务主管金妮
Jeannie, the head of east coast operations Jeannie?
原来我们的孩子上同一所学校
Yeah, turns out our kids go to the same school.
世界真小
Small world huh?
世界真怪
Weird world.
你的孩子
Your kids?
我觉得我的角色应该有孩子
I figure my character has kids.
这句话我没有一个字听懂的
Ya know there isn't a part of that sentence I don't need explained.
演戏的时候  你需要思考这类的事情
Well, see when you're acting you need to think about stuff like that.
我的角色  数据分析员乔瑟夫
My character, Joseph the processor guy,
有两个女儿  阿希莉跟布兰妮
has two little girls, Ashley and Brittany.
布兰妮做什么阿希莉都要学
Ashley copies everything Brittany does.
有时隐形小孩就是那个样子的
Well, invisible kids can be that way sometimes.
乔瑟夫跟他太太凯伦
Yeah. You know Joseph and his wife, Karen,
正考虑再生一个
are thinking of having a third kid...
知道吗  刚刚生了
Ya know what? Just did.
是嘛
Really? Wow.
你那想象的精子  力量一定非常强大
That's some pretty powerful imaginary sperm you must have there.
你知道什么令痒痒加剧吗
You know what makes the itching even worse?
你不停地提到痒这个字吗
That you don't stop talking about it.
好
Fine.
我们专心的玩吧
Let's just play, ok.
好
Good, ok.
要丢了  来两个六  要丢了
Here we go, double sixes, here we go...
要丢了  给老娘来两个六  准备掷骰子
Here we go, come to mama, just getting ready to roll the dice...
你在干什么  你在抓痒吧
What're you doing? Are you scratching?
没有  我在祈求好运
No. This is what I do for luck, ok.
你在抓痒  骰子给我
You're scratching. Give me the dice.
不要
No.
骰子给我
Give me the dice.
不要  扔了  两个六
No. Here. There. Ooh, double sixes.
我们不能抓  你知道的  会留疤的
We can't scratch. You know we can't, we'll scar.
可是我没办法不去想
Uhh, I can't stop thinking about it.
太痒了啦
It's just so hard.
我只想抓住这些房子  磨擦我的全身
I just wanna grab all these houses and rub 'em all over my body.
不可以
No.
给我
Give it.
-不行  -给我
- No. - Yeah, come on.
你知道你要的  你知道你也要  对不对
You know you want it, you know you want it too, come on.
就坏一次吧  包你欲仙欲死
Let's just be bad, it'll feel so good.
来吧  来吧
Come on. Come on.
神啦救救我
Oh God help me.
舒服吧
Good huh?
现在换我了  后面  来吧  用力
Now do me, do my back. Oh come on, harder.
就这样  别动
There you go. Don't move.
为什么  你做什么
Why? What you...
停下  马上停下
Oh, stop that, stop that right now.
我就想到你会这样  菲比
You know, I might have expected this of you Phoebe,
但是莱恩  你是个军人啊
but Ryan, you're a military man.
你跟米顿得来我们的船上玩
You and Milton have to join us on the boat.
凯伦会带午餐  你带孩子们来
Karen'll pack a lunch, you'll bring the kids,
我们好好玩一天
we'll make a day of it.
听起来好棒
Oh, that sounds lovely.
我们得好好安排一下
We're gonna have to set that up.
我最好回去了  希望宝宝好点了
Oh, I better get back. Hope the baby feels better.
谢谢  再见  金妮
Oh, thanks, thanks. Bye bye Jeannie.
再见  乔伊
Bye bye Joey.
好虚伪
What a phony.
我相信她会学乖的
Well, I'm sure you'll teach her a lesson
当她在码头上一脚踩空的时候
when she steps off the dock onto nothing.
道格拉斯先生
Hey Mr. Douglas.
先生
Sir.
听着  宾  备忘录我收到了
Uh, listen Bing, I received your memo.
系统报告下周五才会出来吗
So, we're not gonna receive the systems report until next Friday?
我部门的人希望
Well the people in my group
周末假期能跟家人一起共度
wanna spend the holiday weekend with their families.
我也有家庭  但我还是会上班
I have a family, I'm gonna be here.
是啊  宾  你干嘛呢
Yeah Bing, what's that about?
这是让我的人稍微喘口气  以提高士气
It's about cutting my people a little slack, ya know, for morale.
如果你想看大概的数据
Look, if you wanna see some rough numbers,
我可以在星期三以前给你
I can get them to you by Wednesday.
大概的数据
Rough numbers?
公司不是建立在大概的数据上的
This company was not built on rough numbers.
我说的对吗  道格拉斯先生
Am I right Mr. Douglas.
星期二以前  把最终正确数据放在我桌上
Have the final numbers on my desk by Tuesday.
我会照办的
Uh, if you say so sir.
乔瑟夫很厉害  对不对
Joseph's good, isn't he?
我要杀了你
Well, I'm going to kill you.
我只是觉得乔瑟夫
Hey, hey, I just figure Joseph's
是那种喜欢瞎搅和的人
the kinda guy that likes to mix it up.
兴风作浪  惹是生非
Ya know, get in there, ruffle some feathers.
为什么
Why?
听着  抱歉  但乔瑟夫就是这样的
Look, I'm sorry but that's what Joseph does, ok.
你想耍花招的话  他会揭发你的
If you try to pull somethin', he'll call you on it.
他会说  "你耍什么花招"
"What're you tryin' to pull," he'll say.
胶带  我是不是也该带点什么来
Ooh, duct tape. Was I supposed to bring something too?
是给那对抓痒鸳鸯的
This is for the scratchy twins out there.
我把隔热手套绑在他们手上了
I taped oven mits to their hands.
你真严
You're strict.
这是为他们好啊
It's for their own good.
我很欣赏你有效率的
You know, I like the way you have efficiently
把胶带的末端折起来
folded this tab under.
这样急用胶带的时候
See in a tape emergency
就省下了好几秒宝贵的时间
you could shave valuable seconds off your time.
正是  真高兴在你面前
Exactly. Oh, I love that I can be
我现在可以彻底神经质了
totally neurotic around you now.
告诉我实话
Tell me the truth.
现在你桌上摆的东西都成直角
Don't you like it better now that everything
不是好多了吗
on your desk is perpendicular?
如果不是直角  那就是错角
If it's not a right angle, it is a wrong angle.
很好
Very good.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道吗  明天我要改你的时钟
You know what. Tomorrow I'm gonna do your clocks.
你要怎样改我的时钟
You're gonna do what to my clocks.
我要把它调成我的时间
I'm gonna set them to my time.
我糊涂了  时间不都是一样的吗
Well, I'm confused. I thought we shared time.
不  我把房间的时钟调快了六分钟
No no. See, in my bedroom I set my clock six minutes fast.
想不想知道原因
You wanna know why?
因为卧室跟厨房在不同的时区里
Because it's in a slightly different time zone than the kitchen.
算了  我不想说了
No forget it, I'm not gonna tell you now.
来嘛  告诉我
No come on. Come on tell me.
不  你不会明白的
No. See you don't understand.
说嘛
Come on.
你根本没有任何可爱的小怪癖
No. You don't have any of these cute little obsessive things.
那不对  不对
No that's not true. That is not true.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh yeah. - Yeah.
说一个你的来听听
Alright, well tell me one of yours.
好的
Ok.
我的怪癖是
Ahh. One of my things is,
我总是把运动袜  跟西装袜分开来放
I always separate my sweat socks from my dress socks.
如果搞混了会怎样
What if they get mixed up?
天啊  那我会  我会发狂的
Boy I would just uh, I would freak out.
你才不会  我真不敢相信
You would not. I can't believe this.
真讨厌你那么正常
I hate this, you're too normal.
真不敢相信我的男朋友没怪癖
I can't believe my boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
我的男朋友没有怪癖
My boyfriend doesn't have a thing.
如果这话被人听到  别人会怀疑我无能
See, if anyone overheard that, I didn't come off well there.
道格拉斯先生正在找你
Mr. Douglas is looking for you.
为什么  道格拉斯为什么要找我
Why? Wh- wh- why is Mr. Douglas looking for me?
因为他怀疑
'Cause he has a strong suspicion
你搞砸了那个银行项目
that you dropped the ball on the lender project.
为什么  为什么他要怀疑我
Wha- wh- why, why, why does he suspect that?
因为开始他以为是乔瑟夫的错
Becasue at first he thought it was Joseph.
但在问了乔瑟夫之后  发现原来是你
But after he asked Joseph about it, turns out it was you.
反正我想你应该知道啦
Anyway, I just thought you should know.
好吧  够了
Alright, that's it.
听我说  乔伊  抱歉
Look Joey, I'm sorry,
我知道这是你一生难求的好角色
I realize this is the role of a lifetime for ya,
如果可以只开除乔瑟夫  我会的
and if I could just fire Joseph, I would,
但不幸的是  这不可能  所以
but unfortunately that's not possible so
我必须要你们两个一起走人
I'm gonna have to let both of you go.
你在胡扯什么  大家都爱乔瑟夫
What're you talking about, everybody loves Joseph.
我不爱  我恨乔瑟夫
I don't, I hate Joseph, ok.
我认为他是个马屁精
I think he's a brown-nosing suck up.
是吗  你不能开除乔瑟夫
Oh yeah? Well you can't fire Joseph.
知道为什么吗  因为他不在你的部门
You know why, 'cause he's not in your department.
好吧  我不能开除乔瑟夫
Alright, ok, alright. So I can't fire Joseph
但是我可以睡他老婆
but uh, I can sleep with his wife.
凯伦
Karen.
对  凯伦  我正在考虑跟她搞婚外情
Yeah, Karen. I'm thinking about having an affair with her.
你知道吗  刚搞了
Oh, you know what? I just did.
你对我做了什么  老兄
What the hell are you doing to me man.
不是我  是我的角色  钱迪干的
Oh well it's not me, it's my character, Chandy.
无赖分析员  为了好玩勾引同事老婆
Yeah the rogue processor who seduces his co-worker's wives for sport
隔天在饮水机旁边当笑话讲
and then laughs about it the next day at the water cooler.
其实她的内裤就在我的抽屉里
In fact, I have her panties right there in my drawer.
真的吗
Really?
假的  疯子  根本没有这个人
No freakshow, she's fictional.
别激动  对你很重要的话
Take it easy. If it means that much to you,
那我找别的事做好了
I'll uh, I'll go find something else.
谢谢你
Thank you.
只是我会想念乔瑟夫的  我喜欢他
It's just that, I, I'm gonna miss Joseph. I liked him.
他的太太  好正点
His wife, she was hot.
我能取掉这个吗  我发誓我不抓了
Can I please take these off? I swear I won't scratch.
对不起  莫妮卡的命令
No sorry hon, Monica's orders.
真不容易
Well that wasn't easy.
晚餐好了
Ok, dinner's on.
烤箱里还有一个黄桃馅饼在加热
And there's a peach cobbler warming in the oven
盘子会很烫手  但那应该不成问题
so the plate's gonna be hot but that shouldn't be a problem for you.
好了  孩子们  拜拜
Alright you kids, bye now.
拜拜
Bye.
看  低成本的木偶剧
Oh look, a low budget puppet show.
真可惜你看不到  我举起的是哪一根手指
It's such a shame you can't see which finger I'm holding up.
酒
Wine?
麻烦你
Please.
洒出来了
Oh, I spilled some.
我来
I got it.
我得告诉你  你今晚好美
I must tell you, you look beautiful tonight.
你说什么
What?
对不起
Sorry.
你好美
You look beautiful.
我受够了
You know what, that's it, that's it.
爽
Yes.
你们...
Hey you guys...
莫妮卡  醒醒  莫妮卡
Monica, wake up. Monica.
什么事
What's up?
我想到一个了
I thought of a thing.
是吗
Yeah?
对  我必须睡...
Yeah. I have to sleep,
必须睡床的这一边
have to, on this side of the bed.
不  亲爱的  你必须睡床的那一边
No honey. You have to sleep on this side of the bed
是因为我必须睡床的这一边
because I have to sleep on this side of the bed.
还是因为我让你这么以为呢
Or so I would have you believe.
没什么大不了的  你喜欢睡床的一边
No. Big deal, so you have a side of the bed,
每个人都有自己喜欢的一边
everybody has a side of the bed.
你还没听我的理由呢
Hey come on, you haven't heard my reason yet.
好啊  说吧
Alright, go on.
我必须睡在床的西边
Ok, I have to sleep on the west side
因为我在加州长大
because I grew up in California
睡东边的话  海洋的方向就错了
and otherwise the ocean would be on the wrong side.
天啊  你真变态
Oh my God, you're a freak.
你觉得怎么样
Yeah. How 'bout that.
莱恩  你这次要潜到哪里
So uh, Ryan, were you shipping off to?
我真的不能说
I really can't say.
那你们潜水艇上有核武器吗
So do you have like any nuclear weapons on board?
我不能说
I can't say.
那你是不是可以
Well do you get to look through one of those
用那种潜望镜看东西
like, those periscope thingys.
对不起  我不能说
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
学潜水艇的知识真酷
Wow, it, it's neat learning about submarines.
我该走了  不然会错过飞机
I better get out of here, I'm gonna miss my flight.
我送你出去
Ok, I'll walk you out.
拜拜  莱恩
Bye Ryan.
-幸会了  -见到你真好
- Pleasure. - It was nice to meet you.
保重
Take care.
我们可以弄套制服给你穿吗
So do you uh, think we can get you one of those uh, uniform things?
你喜欢是不是
You like that do ya?
是呀
Oh yeah.
-我去打电话  -好的
- I'll make some calls. - Ok.
我们的两个礼拜居然就这样过完了
Can you believe how we spent our two weeks together?
我知道  我计划的浪漫事一件也没做
I know. We didn't do any of the romantic things I had planned, like
比如说去中央公园野餐
having a picnic at Central Park and ya know,
在中央公园咖啡馆喝咖啡
coffee at Central Perk.
我们刚喝过了
Oh I just got that.
计程车
Taxi.
再见
Bye you.
对不起  我们打烊了
Oh I'm sorry, we're clo-...
你好  水兵哥
Hey sailor.
这是你心里想的吗
Is this what you had in mind?
可不是
I'll say.
我明天就要出航了
I'm shipping out tomorrow.
那么
Well then uh,
春宵就别虚度了
we better make this night count.
等等  我忘了关咖啡机
Oh wait, I forgot to turn off the cappucino machine.
起航吧
Anchors away.
等等  我的包  我的包...
Oh no no, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse, my purse.
我忘了关洗手间的灯
Oh, you know what. I forgot to turn off the bathroom light.
我们干脆楼上见好了
Alright you know, why don't I just meet you upstairs.
亲爱的
Honey.